minishares.org 2016-04-06

# Privacy Policy | Minishares

### Personal Information

We automatically receive certain types of information when you interact with our Web pages, services and communications. This information includes your computer or digital device’s IP address, access times, your browser type and language, type of operating system you use, your account activity and accessed pages. These information are logged and used by Minishares for purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Security of information

The security of your information is important to us. We employ appropriate security measures in place to protect information collected from loss, destruction, disclosure, unauthorized access, misuse and alteration. Although we strive to protect your personal information, Minishares cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

### Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

### Links to third party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

### Your consent

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of these information by Minishares. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, Contact Us.
